{
    "id": "87453b6757b645ae93977075e68172d9",
    "title": "Future Tense Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The train ……………….. at 6 pm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leaves",
                "will leave",
                "would leave"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d922a122e9404723bcb32ca5dda03764"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will phone you when I ………………….. time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will have",
                "have",
                "would have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "375dc214f71c4beebb239e3ec44bb5a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… my grandparents this evening.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visit",
                "will visit",
                "am visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "58dcf8e73c3049e69a1c230be27be036"
        },
        {
            "question": "Look at the sky. It ……………………. to rain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will go",
                "goes",
                "is going"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a87d0068839b4f1e9935fbc3dbd20f9f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Perhaps we ………………….. Paris next month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visit",
                "will visit",
                "are visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a5c8fec0d0464acf9176b8ec777cbb89"
        },
        {
            "question": "Unless we ……………………. now we can’t be there on time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "start",
                "will start",
                "started"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "aaa384a6145c449f95e8f47a3f7c776a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The next term ………………….. on September 15th.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "begin",
                "begins",
                "will begin"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9aadd3697f034573a532de772facb892"
        },
        {
            "question": "Oh dear! I ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will sneeze",
                "sneeze",
                "am going to sneeze"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "88c26f3ad8a64bfc9a0364e1f432c895"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am sure he ……………………. win.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "will be"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "303d71fd523243469d4590226042cbe8"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ……………………. you one of these days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "are seeing",
                "will be seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "11063d14faa14bbe95afc4039f874b52"
        }
    ]
}